Contact

www.linkedin.com/in/natashadevaud (LinkedIn) natashadevaud.squarespace.com/ demo-reel-1 (Other) natashadevaud.squarespace.com/ resume (Other)

Top Skills

Lighting
Look Development
Virtual Costume Design

Languages

English (Native or Bilingual) French (Native or Bilingual)

Natasha Devaud

Technical Director at Industrial Light + Magic

San Rafael, California, United States

Summary

3D Artist/Technical Director with extensive experience in visual effects for movies (Star Wars, Harry Potter, Avengers, Transformers, ...) as well as animated movies (Rango, Strange Magic).

Specialized in lighting and look development, excellent aesthetic interpretation, experience in compositing and texturing.

Experience in 3D clothing simulation (Marvelous Designer), with a good understanding of patterns, garment construction and fabric properties.

Experience in textile/surface design and illustration.

Excellent communication skills, highly organized, work well within a team and can take on small leadership roles, very productive.

Accomplished sewer and costume maker, knowledge of millinery and jewelry making as well as many textile techniques.

Background in fashion design and education.

My dream job: join a highly creative project combining 3D visual effects with amazing costume design and fantastic environments to bring the audience to a new level of sensory exploration.

Experience

Meta

Visual Designer

January 2022 - Present (1 year 4 months)

Sausalito, California, United States

Academy of Art University Instructor September 2018 - Present (4 years 8 months) San Francisco Bay Area

The Lazy Giraffe
3D Graphic Artist
January 2018 - Present (5 years 4 months)

Page 1 of 3

San Rafael CA

WHISKYTREE

Technical Director

October 2021 - December 2021 (3 months)

San Rafael, California, United States

Dreamscape Immersive

Senior Art Lead

September 2020 - July 2021 (11 months)

Geneva, Switzerland

Virtual costume design and lighting for multiple users' VR experiences.

Artanim

VR Costume Designer

March 2020 - July 2020 (5 months)

Geneva, Switzerland

Modeling and texturing of clothes for VR characters, using Marvelous

Designer, Maya, Zbrush and Substance Painter.

WHISKYTREE

Technical Director

February 2019 - June 2019 (5 months)

San Rafael CA

WHISKYTREE

Technical Director

October 2017 - December 2017 (3 months)

San Rafael CA

Industrial Light & Magic

Senior Technical Director

1995 - August 2017 (22 years)

San Francisco

Rhythm & Hues

3D TD

February 1994 - June 1995 (1 year 5 months)

Education

ECAL - Ecole cantonale d'art de Lausanne Master's Degree, Computer Graphics · (1991 - 1993)

Ecole Formes et Couleurs Fashion Design · (1990 - 1991)

Ecole Normale II BA, Education · (1985 - 1989)